[{"answer": "Oh, not at all.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "So, Kim McKerreghan and Mary Poret, your daughters have known each other for years, and did you have any concerns about them going on vacation together?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "The last time and the only time I've heard from my daughter was on Monday.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "What was the communications?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Monday I told --", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "But what did they tell you?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Right now I think we just want them home and want them in our arms.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "I mean, what do you want to make it better?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I sure did.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Did one of you bring antibiotics?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "You don't have a lot.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "So as an American traveler, what do you got?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It does a great deal.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Does insurance really help you?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Don't we have to have some perspective here about how many thousands and thousands do go out on the waters and it's OK?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Can you give us that?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "It's a terrible sight thinking of people trapped on a ship with limited food.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Are we going to have to see a lot of sales for people to go OK, I'll board again?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Yes, I think what -- you can judge that once everybody is back home and see how they actually react to the complaints, react to any oversight the government tries to impose or any --", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "In your opinion, are they doing enough?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't think so.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Is that wise to do to come armed with antibiotics even though you don't know if anyone is sick?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "So which is the most pressing?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "-- that's not very -- no, I can't.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Can you imagine?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Yes, they usually have just one physician on board, at most two physicians.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "But I do wonder for a ship with 4,000 people on board, how many medical personnel you do have there on a regular basis and can they handle what their -- what is presented to them?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "We're fine.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I did watch the state of the union address last night.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Did you, by any chance, hear what the president said in the state of the union regarding gun control and did you have an opinion about what he said?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say drastically different, and I'm not an expert in any aspect of guns.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "When you hear about gun control, and obviously this is a huge issue -- it was before, but even more now, did you feel a certain way before the shooting and now drastically different or no -- regarding that issue?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Again, I think it's a much broader topic than just that.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "So your issue is more about the types of guns that we are allowed to have legally, not about the people who are getting weapons illegally?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Exactly, Robin, yes.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "And the Sandy Hook promise was supposed to be a discussion about what to do, but also you guys have an idea about how to let people in Newtown, even on Valentine's Day know that the rest of us are thinking about them?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "No, dance.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "So when you say rise up, you mean what, demonstrate or dance or?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "In the weeks and months leading up to this date -- I didn't in the beginning.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "So when you see that, how does a one-day event where people are moving -- how does it have the potential to impact, first of all, those young lives in that picture and the others in the 205 countries taking part?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "It's kind of Rupert Murdoch that's been marinated a long time in Ted Turner.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Are you going to be back?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Yeah, Ted --", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Ted?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a voting member of the Motion Picture Academy, so I see everything.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Do you have some picks?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Well, tomorrow, but in some places tomorrow is already today -- starting on the 14th, which has already happened in Samoa, where they're rising, and the Philippines and Australia, where they're rising, go out in the streets and join your fellow country people and dance and pray and chant and sing and say no more, no more violence against women and girls.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "By the way, how can the viewers take part if they wanted to?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Oh definitely.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "But the environment may be one of them, yes?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "You know, no, no, no.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "So when you heard the president speak last night about climate change and that we must do something about climate change, was that enough for you?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "How do you pronounce it?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I fall for that.", "docId": "130213pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "You know, when your wife says nothing, nothing, honey, you know not to fall for that, right?", "qSentId": 634}]